Guide to the Jennings Wood collection of Confederate imprints, 1862-1865 MS2127
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 4, Folder 1363)
  Letter of Secretary of War Dec. 8, 1864, [conveying information relative to the amount of money expended in the payment of the Army of the Trans-Mississippi since the assignment of Gen. E. K. Smith to the command. Richmond, 1864]. 4 p. 24 V2 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 4, Folder 1364)
  Letter of Secretary of War Dec. 13, 1864, [requesting that the amount required to pay for horses of volunteers be increased to four millions of dollars. Richmond, 1864]. 2 p. 23 cm.
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 4, Folder 1432)
  Report of the Secretary of WarNovember 3, 1864. 36 p. 22 1/2 cm. Richmond 1864
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1864 (Box 4, Folder 1436)
  Response of Secretary of War, to the resolutions of the Senate, adopted December 5th, 1864, respecting operations under the act of 6th February, 1864December 10, 1864. [Richmond, 1864]. 2, 2 p. 24
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 1865 (Box 4, Folder 2377)
  Resolutions of Wise's Brigade, [n.p. 1865.] 3 p. 25 cm. (3 copies)
- Jennings Wood Confederate Imprint, 01/30/1865 (Box 4, Folder 2728)
  DeJarnette, Daniel C:The Monroe doctrine. Speech of JJpn. D.C. DeJarnette, of Virginia, in the Confederate House of Representatives, January 30th, 1865, pending negotiations for peace. [Richmond? 1865.] 20 p. 22 cm.